Ke garisan,
sedia
dan
mula!
Ke garisan,
sedia
dan
mula!
Ke garisan,
sedia
dan
mula!
Ke garisan,
sedia
dan
mula!
Berlari
Berlari dengan pantas, ah tunggu!
Tunggu
sebentar
Being dejected or unheard of, I'm not like that
At all, don't get worn out! Don't mind!
Beginnings are important, but
but I end up taking too big of a leap and fall down with a crash
this is no good, I'm such a failure
Oh tuhan tolonglah aku!
tidak menyedarinya bagai orang bodoh,
I was roped in three, two, one and it dawns on me!
tiga、
dua、
satu、
tiga、
dua、
satu、
eh eh eh, adakah aku tertipu?!
Sangat berbeza dari yang aku bayangkan!
"This can't be..."
but I only panic for a moment;
this is, in its own way, pretty fun.
my school life is waiting, right?
the world is far from boring or monotonous
Pastinya
ia tak akan pudar
Aku merasakan kisah aku
baru sahaja
Ber
mula
!
Berjalan melangkah
selepas sekolah
Atau apa je lah
Buat apa sahaja
yang kau mahu!
akhirnya
ter hubung
look, be pleasantly
swept away in the enthusiasm
Hijau hijau hijau
seperti ditandakan signal
I'll continue to run through the present!
da!
uniquely special, strangely different, is this 2D?
each incident has a meaning
astonished, dumbfounded, the fact is,
I almost can't keep up with this!
my start dash was an absolute failure,
I kick out ungracefully, absurdity is a required lesson.
this is risky, I'm no good!
but it's nothing but fun!
there's no textbook for common sense, it's just as you see
but, it's a strangely unrivaled youth you wouldn't usually experience
an after-school stride hop step jumping
jumping up high, just as I imagined
A mild breakthrough, someday, I'll draw the answer
I'll take a step forward,
And maybe catch a cold, but
Blue Blue Blue Facing towards the end of the sky
I'll shoot out with a toy gun
da!
On, 1, 2, 3 "Let's Go!"
On, un, deux, trois "Let's Go!"
On, Ii, ar, san "Let's Go!"
On, eins, zwei, drei "Let's Go!"
I can't think of anything else "Let's Go!"
Just go already, "Let's Go!"
Motivation to the MAX! go~!
Look, just push out your hand
And do whatever you want to do
Link Ring Link is finally connected to Ring Link
Look, be pleasant
Swept away in the enthusiasm
Green Green Green just as the signal indicates,
I'm continuing to run through the present!
I'll shoot out with a toy gun!
da!
One more time!
Yeah!